{"data":[{"question":"Helen doesn't like the picture ___ for her.","a":"to draw","b":"drawing","c":"to be drawn","d":"drawn","answer":"4","explain":"\n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts. The pattern looks like this: main clause + participle phrase ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"You had better _________ your hair ___ after school.","a":"have, cut","b":"had, cut","c":"to have, to cut","d":"to have, cut","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Had better do something\n- Have something done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Everything ___ from a distance appears rather small.","a":"seen","b":"seeing","c":"see","d":"to see","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause: sometime we can ignore \"which\/that\/who... + be\" \n+ Everything seen from...= everything which is seen from...","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody likes to drink cold ___ water in winter.","a":"being boiled","b":"boiling","c":"to be boiling","d":"boiled","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past participle can play a role as an adjective","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A lot of readers have read the editorial ___ by Lisa.","a":"wrote","b":"write","c":"written","d":"writing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause: sometime we can ignore which\/that\/ who","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Vincent found a dog ___ to a telegraph pole.","a":"to tie","b":"tie","c":"tied","d":"tying","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause: sometime we can ignore which\/that\/ who","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Did a company _________ \"I'm Publishing\" ring me up this morning?","a":"called","b":"call","c":"calling","d":"calls","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause: sometime we can ignore which\/that\/ who","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The linguists of an institute are said ___ folk songs in the countryside.","a":"collected","b":"collecting","c":"to have collected","d":"to have been collecting","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: be said to do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you go to the celebration ___ on New Year's Eve?","a":"to be holding","b":"held","c":"being held","d":"to be held","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice in relative clause, sometime we can ignore which\/that\/ who","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The LCD TV is a ___ electrical equipment.","a":"newly-invented","b":"newly-inventing","c":"newly-invention","d":"newly-invent","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past participle can play a role as an adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}